data, when you look at the hydradenitis superativa NBRX naive share, you can see here pretty
consistently around 50%. We did see a slight dip in January because of the re-verification
and the availability of biosimilars. We see that now climbing back up. So we expect to be stable
in that 50% range. Importantly as well for IV patient share, we see steady growth up to now
14%. And so both of these will continue to be important. We are hoping that the HS market
continues to develop, not just for cosentics, but as we'll address later, remirutinib now
will also have a readout later this year in HS. So we want to see this market expand so the patients
who need better therapies are getting them. Outside of the US, we were up 3%. That's
primarily driven by growth in Europe. We're up 3% in the U.S. and we're up 3% in the U.S.
and emerging markets. We continue to see competitive pressures in China with multiple
local NRDL entrants. And so there's a long list of competitors that we have. And we've had very
strong share performance in China now over many years, but our goal will be to maintain now
share and hopefully can stabilize as well the performance in China over the coming quarters.
We continue to advance the new indications. Importantly, the PMR submission,
it happened across geographies and we expect the FDA approval in the second half.
And we also received FDA approval for the pediatric HS indication, and we completed EMA
submission as well. So all on track on that front. So moving to slide 12, I wanted to just say a few
words on our renal portfolio by talking about each of the key brands. So first, let's talk about
Fabhalta. Sales were up 103% in quarter one with NBRX leadership now, both in PNH and C3G. In PNH,
NBRX share, as well as important and significant contributions from some of our key ex-US markets.
In C3G, 56% NBRX share, and we're now approved in 46 countries. So both of those indications really
having solid and consistent performance. Now importantly, in IGAN, I think we believe our
uptake in US patients will continue to build and with patients with persistent proteinuria
and glomerular inflammation. So here we're at later line therapy. But I think very
important was the two-year phase three APLAUSE IGAN data, which was published in the New England
Journal. It showed an impressive slowing in kidney function decline of 49% versus placebo,